[SAD]😢 you were made to be ruled in the end it will be
[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 [SAD]😢 every man for himself what do we
do we get ready
[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 [SAD]😢 there was an idea to bring
together a group of remarkable people
[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 so when we needed them
[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 [SAD]😢 they could fight the battles that
we never could gentlemen what are
[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 [SAD]😢 you prepared to do no offense
but i don't play well with others big man in a suit
[SAD]😢 armor take that away what are you uh genius
[LAUGHTER]😂 [SAD]😢 billionaire playboy philanthropist if
we can't protect the earth i'm sure we'll
[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 avenge it
dr banner your work is unparalleled and i'm a huge fan
of
the way you
[MUSIC/heroic]🎵 [SAD]😢 lose control and turn into an
enormous green rage monster thanks